http://campgreystone.com/privacy-policy

General Information
Cabin Requests & AssignmentsBunks & DecoratingBirthdaysWrite Your PenpalPackage PolicyVisitor PolicyLaundry & ValuablesPersonal Allowance & Store
Opening & Closing Day
Opening DayClosing DayCamper Luggage
Packing & Preparing
Packing for CampPreparing for CampHomesicknessSchedulingRiding & RaftingPlaces to StayUseful LinksDriving Directions
During the Summer
Summer PhotosLiveStreamContacting Your Camper
Air Travel
Air TravelUnaccompanied MinorAir DepartureFlight Change Notice
Greystone's History
Timeline100 ThingsGreen & GoldOnline ArchiveSongsBanquetsGreatest HitsDecade Quiz
Greystone's People
A Celebration of ServiceFashion Through the YearsTell Your Story
Privacy Policy
This is the privacy policy for Camp Greystone. Your privacy is very important to us. Our homepage is located at www.campgreystone.com. Please contact us with any questions or concerns.
Collection
Our online data management is handled by our professional partners at CampMinder. The full text of their privacy policy is available here.
Distribution and management
Neither Camp Greystone, our webmaster Ronningen Design, nor CampMinder re-use or distribute any information that is gathered during your online experience at the Camp Greystone website. It is therefore not necessary for our visitors to opt-in, or opt-out, of use of the information gathered online by Camp Greystone, our webmaster, or Camper Connection, LLC.
We collect personal information for verification & technical support purposes only.
We do not disclose, sell, or rent information that you may give us to any outside companies or organizations. Our online services are secure and available only to bona fide members of the Camp Greystone community. Our visitors are encouraged to report any discrepancies or unsavory behavior to:
The camp office,
Camp Greystone
21 Camp Greystone Lane
Zirconia, NC 28790
(828) 693-3182 (TEL)
(828) 693-1562 (FAX)
our webmaster,
Ronningen Design
300 D N. Main St., Suite 202
Hendersonville, NC 28792
(828) 693-1924 (TEL)
or our technology partner
CampMinder
37 Silver Spruce
Boulder, CO 80306
(303) 444-CAMP (TEL)
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.
Dispute resolution and privacy seals
Contact the camp office by .
Data collection
P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as “statements”). This policy contains 1 data group.
Group: Any Interactions
Data we collect
We collect the following information:
Active data collection via user input
Physical contact information (Name, mailing address & telephone)
Online contact information (Email address)
Purchase information (Name, mailing address, email address, telephone, fax & credit card info)
Passive data collection via cookies & HTTP Headers
Computer information
HTTP cookies
Last URI requested by the user
State management mechanisms
What we do with the data
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
Web site and system administration.
Research and development.
Who uses the data
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents only. We do not share any of our data with third parties.
Other important information
We do not condition participation in the online activities at www.campgreystone.com on disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary.
Parents may review the information collected from their children at any time by contacting one of the parties listed above. A parent may request to have their child’s personal information/account removed at any time by contacting one of the parties listed above. Furthermore, a parent may request that Camp Greystone stop future collection or use of a child’s data by contacting one of the parties listed above.
Cookies
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:
Site administration
Completing the user’s current activity
Copyright
Unless otherwise noted, this website and all of the content it contains is copyright © Camp Greystone 2015.
